[bird screeches]
This is it, Gon. My brother sent the URL.
That’s awesome! Let’s get started!
Yeah!
[theme song playing]
GATHERING x OF x HEROES
[narrator] As Kurapika
sets out on the path
to face the Phantom Troupe
and avenge the Kurta,
Gon and Killua are also busy
making their own preparations
for the auction in Yorknew City.
INTERNET CAFÉ
[Gon] Is this the Hunter website?
Yeah. I’ve heard that Hunters worldwide
post lots of information here.
Worldwide? Really?
That’s pretty amazing.
[computer]
Please swipe your Hunter’s License
and enter your license code.
[beeps]
[Gon typing]
[door creaking]
[Killua]
Put the cursor on the bartender.
[bartender]
What kind of information do you want?
Wow! That’s a lot of info!
Click "game category."
There it is. Greed Island.
Price is 20 million Jenny.
Twenty million?
I guess they won’t give out information
for free.
All right. I guess we gotta.
Okay then, I’m depositing 20 million.
I can feel aura coming from the monitor!
Then to enter the site...
it looks like you actually
have to be a Nen user.
Okay. Now listen very carefully.
Y’see, Greed Island
is a game created by Nen users.
It appears that there are
multiple creators
whose motives are unclear.
They infused Nen into
all hundred copies of the game.
Nen activates on startup,
pulling the player inside the game itself.
Wait. Inside the game?
[bartender]
Only Nen users can actually play it.
As long as the player stays alive
within the game,
the console will continue to run,
even if the game is unplugged.
It will stop if the player dies.
There was one owner...
who hired fifty Hunters to give it a shot.
And of the 50...
not a single one ever came back.
I heard you can return
if you can find a save point.
Is that true?
It’s from the Hunter website.
It’s gotta be accurate.
At the Yorknew City auction,
there are going to be
seven units of Greed Island
and every one of them
will be available for purchase.
Of course, the lowest starting bid
is 8.9 billion Jenny.
8.9 billion?
The price has skyrocketed!
That’s three billion more
than we’d pay for retail!
Getting one’s ranked level G.
[both] Huh?
The game is considered a legend,
but there are still
plenty of units around.
If you have enough money,
it should be relatively easy
to procure one.
Hmm... A G-rank, huh?
That’s lower than I thought.
You’re telling me, if I can’t even
get my hands on a simple game,
I’ll never be able to find you.
Right, Ging?
[Killua] Still, the money’s a big problem.
Hey. This auction…
Do you think
that we can participate in it?
At 8.9 billion?
C’mon, that’s way out of our league!
Uh-huh. Not to go buy stuff, but to sell.
Selling, huh? That’s it!
We can go look for treasure
and then auction off
whatever we manage to find.
Yes!
We can start with the 800 million
that we earned fighting at Heavens Arena
and go from there.
Hmm.
First off,
we’ll try the online flea markets
and auction websites.
Now, let’s see what we can dig up.
We’ll increase our funds
and then, get a copy of Greed Island!
Yeah!
-Yeah!
-All right!
[both laughing]
How much... is left?
Between the two of us,
we’re at 10.84 million.
[both sigh]
What the hell?
When we first started,
we were making a decent amount.
I knew this would happen.
That’s why I told you
we should stick to the reputable sites.
I couldn’t help myself!
The risky sites are the only real way
to make a profit!
[both sigh]
This isn’t working out so good.
[man] Now, then…
show me what you’ve brought.
Hair from the famous actress, Sara.
DNA authenticated.
Taken from an Egypersian pyramid.
It’s a mummy’s right arm.
The Scaly skin of a Dracoderma patient.
The skull of a unicorn tribesman.
Okay, then.
Congratulations,
all four of you are hired.
My name is Dalzollene,
the head bodyguard.
You start now.
I look forward
to working with each of you.
Your mission
is to safely escort the boss
to a Yorknew City hotel room.
A private airship
will take you all to Lingon,
an airport outside of Yorknew.
From the airport, it’s ninety minutes
to get to the hotel.
A car will be waiting.
The four of you will be assigned
to provide the outer ring of security.
Any questions?
Do you know
who might be targeting the boss?
That question’s not deserving
of an answer.
[Kurapika] What do you mean?
The boss is a VIP in the underworld.
There are plenty who hold a grudge.
Since you didn’t understand,
I’ll rephrase.
Grudges aside,
can you think of anyone
who might actually commit to an attack?
Anyone at all?
If we can identify the candidates,
their styles and motives,
we can prepare…
helping us to ensure
the boss’s protection.
[Dalzollene] Kurapika, is it?
You are the one who doesn’t understand.
Our job is to protect the boss,
no matter who, when,
where or how they attack.
That's all you need to know! Got it?
So, don’t bother
building a mental profile.
Everyone who approaches is an enemy.
It’s time to meet the boss.
Come on.
[Baise] Excuse me. What’s that?
[Basho] It’s a little too realistic.
-That is an actual human being.
-[all gasp]
He used to be a fellow bodyguard.
But he ignored my advice
and was fooled by false information,
putting the other bodyguards
and the boss at risk.
And so, he was punished accordingly.
You were all brought in
to be his replacements.
Let's go.
Boss. I’ve brought the new bodyguards.
Come in.
[Dalzollene] The boss, Miss Neon.
[all four gasp]
[giggles] New hires!
It’s a pleasure to meet you!
[Basho] Well, anyway,
I was pretty surprised
when we met the boss.
[Baise] No kidding.
They called her an important figure
in the underworld,
so I thought it’d be someone intimidating,
but she turned out to be
a cute little girl.
[footsteps approaching]
[both] Huh?
Pakunoda! Hey, how’ve you been?
[Pakunoda] Long time no see, Shalnark.
You too, Phinks.
[snorts]
You sure took your time getting here.
Oh? Right on time by my watch.
You were supposed to arrive here
ten minutes early.
Same for you guys.
[Shalnark] Bonolenov! Kortopi!
So, you’re going with us, too?
[man] Hey!
Haven’t seen you in quite a while.
I’m reporting for duty, boss.
What’s our target this time?
I’m itchin’ for our new orders!
[Shalnark chuckles] Easy now, Uvo.
Feitan’s group won’t be arriving
until evening.
We’ll wait until everyone’s here.
[Pakunoda] Impatient as usual.
Damn. That’s an entire
half day of waiting.
Hey! If it isn’t Shizuku.
Hello.
-Has the other new addition arrived yet?
-Dunno.
You should ask Machi.
[Dalzollene] This is for September.
What’s this? Seems like there’s a lot.
It is.
Both Mister Trink and Mister Rottfelli
would like their fortunes told.
Aw… That sucks.
I told you I was gonna quit
if you added any more.
And I do apologize.
Your father counts them both
among his closest associates.
Well? Where is Papa, anyway?
He had a very pressing meeting
to attend to.
He’s probably off hunting or playing golf.
[line ringing]
Papa? This is Neon.
What? No way!
You can’t fool me that easily!
No. No!
Huh?
Hmm...
Fine, if you keep your word.
But break one more promise,
and I’ll quit for real!
Hooray! I’m getting
another piece of treasure!
[chuckles] Sweet deal, huh?
Well, congratulations.
‘Kay… now that that’s settled,
I’ll get this over with.
LOVELY GHOSTWRITER:
ANGELIC AUTO WRITING
[Basho] I heard somewhere
that she’s an incredible fortune teller.
Thanks to her father’s connections,
she’s got some VIP clients
in the underworld.
You have it backwards.
That so?
I’d say that the father has used
his daughter
to increase his standing
and move up in the underworld.
And that’s why the prospect of losing her
is so frightening to him.
He’s afraid his enemies might retaliate
by targeting his daughter.
Okay, all done.
Here.
Excellent work.
Tomorrow’s auction starts at night,
doesn’t it?
I want to go shopping beforehand.
If that’s what you want,
I shall accompany you.
How many years has it been, I wonder…
since all 13 of the Troupe members
got together?
Feitan?
Three years, two months.
But two have changed since then.
Numbers four and eight
are different.
Machi. Do you...
think number four, Hisoka,
will actually show up?
No idea.
Don't ask me.
[Franklin] Wasn't he your responsibility?
I just told him to be here.
[Feitan] I don't like Hisoka.
Why does the boss let him do
as he pleases?
For his skills, probably.
[snorts] Skills?
Well, his Bungee Gum
is certainly very impressive.
It would be difficult
for anyone to counter.
[Feitan] Are you saying
that the boss is afraid of Hisoka?
Watch yourself.
[Nobunaga] That’s not what I meant.
Quit being generous.
You’re giving the guy way too much credit.
[scoffs]
Talk is as cheap as it ever was.
Shut up...
or this is what happens, Nobunaga.
You were talking just
as much as I was, Franklin.
-Here we go again.
-[Feitan] Ignore them.
They’re just playing around.
[Machi] So, why is the chief
calling everyone together, anyway?
[Feitan] We’re thieves,
I assume he wants us to steal something.
[Machi] Well, that much I know.
[Dalzollene] Yes.
We’ve arrived safely at the hotel.
But one of the young mistress’s fortunes
concerns me…
“In the basement where prices rise,
your bed shall be made with your brothers.
Do not descend stairs
you have never climbed.
In numbers, do not compete with others.”
And there are three other poems
that begin with the same verse,
meaning that all four of the clients
received fortunes
that are nearly identical.
It seems the only thing
that connects them
is that at this year’s
Underground Auction,
each one of them will be attending.
[Nostrade] So, the fortune says
their lives are at risk,
should they choose to participate?
I think the "sleep" imagery is a metaphor
for illness or for death.
[Nostrade] Understood.
I will pass the fortunes
along to the clients.
There’s one more thing, sir…
The young mistress is never able
to remember the fortunes she’s told,
and she cannot tell her own.
Does it make sense
to let her take part in the auction?
[Nostrade] No! Bring her back immediately!
However, without a proper explanation,
she won’t listen to a word I say.
And if she throws a tantrum,
we won’t be able to stop her.
[laughs]
In any case,
do not take her to the auction.
Send some bodyguards
to place the bids instead.
[Dalzollene] Understood.
[sighs heavily]
[Nostrade] Neon...
[Phinks clicking tongue]
He isn’t coming.
[Feitan] The sun is almost up.
[Uvogin] Dammit, Hisoka.
Next time I see him,
I’ll tear him apart.
[Hisoka] Oh, dear…
That sounds quite gruesome indeed.
I’m simply terrified.
Hisoka, you bastard!
Guess you’re running a bit late.
[Machi]
I was starting to think you wouldn’t show.
Why wouldn’t I?
You asked me to come, didn’t you?
Had I broken my promise,
I would never have the pleasure
of seeing your Nen Stitches again.
-[Machi snorts]
-Okay, boss. Everyone’s here!
Well, boss?
What are we stealing this time?
We will take the treasures
of the Underground Auction.
Which treasures do you want?
Ancient texts, maybe?
The boss does like books.
[Feitan] No. But perhaps games.
There will be many copies
of the most expensive game ever.
Wouldn’t it be more logical
to take precious metals and gemstones?
[boss] All of it.
We'll be taking everything
that's up for auction.
Hold on, boss.
Are you serious?
The Underground Auction is operated
by gangs from all over the world!
Just think about it!
If we do that, we’re gonna make enemies
out of every last one of ‘em!
Are you scared, Uvogin?
No way! I’m ecstatic!
I can’t stop shaking!
Come on! Give us the order, boss!
I want it now!
I give you permission to kill them all.
Anyone who dares to get in our way.
[Uvogin roaring]
[Dalzollene] Good work.
I have your next assignment.
You must win the three items on this list
at the Underground Auction.
Money is no object.
The intact mummy of Princess Corco.
A tissue used by the actor
Sonne Limarch,
with a certificate of DNA authenticity.
-[groans]
-[Dalzollene] And...
the eyes of a Kurta,
known as the Scarlet Eyes.
[shuddering breath]
Also, we’ve received information
that there might be an attack
on the auction.
So be prepared for any contingency,
but keep your focus
on the primary objective
of obtaining these items.
They're coming.
They’re definitely coming!
[narrator] Kurapika eagerly awaits
his revenge against the Phantom Troupe,
a band of murdering thieves.
The sun has risen
on the first day of the auction,
where all sides will soon collide.
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Coming up:
-Gon...
-[Killua] ...and Killua’s…
[both] Hunterpedia!
-I’m Gon!
-I’m Killua!
[both] And this is Hunterpedia!
Today, we’re introducing Neon,
the daughter of the head
of the Nostrade family.
She’s a Flesh Collector!
Her Nen ability’s
the "Lovely Ghostwriter."
I think I’d try to tell my own fortune.
[Gon] Turns out you can’t do that.
[Gon] Next time: "Defend x And x Attack"!
Killua! Are you better
at defending or attacking?
-[Killua] What do you think?
-[Gon] Um... attacking?
[Killua] Bingo.